'use strict';

const STORE = [
  {
    question: "What band wrote the hit song “American Woman”?",
    answers: ["The Who","SteppenWolf","The Band","The Guess Who"],
     correctAnswer: "The Guess Who"
  },
  {
    question: "Eric Clapton’s black stratocaster is famously nicknamed?",
    answers:["Ol Blackie","Lucille","Amanda","Blackie"],
    correctAnswer:"Blackie"
  },
  {
    question:"The lyric Roy Orbison singing for the lonely, that’s me and I want you only comes from what Bruce Springsteen song?",
    answers:["Born to Run","Born In The USA","Thunder Road","Dancing in the Dark"],correctAnswer: "Thunder Road"
  },
  {
    question: "What Kris Kristofferson song was made famous by Janis Joplin?",
    answers:["Sunday Mornin Comin Down","Bobby McGee","Little Girl Blue","Piece of My Heart"],correctAnswer:"Bobby McGee"
  },
  {
    question: "How old was Jimi Hendrix when he died?",
    answers:['25','27','32','28'],
    correctAnswer:'27'
  },
  {
    question:"Bob Dylan wrote what song in 1967 that was later made famous by Jimi Hendrix?",
    answers:["All Along The Watchtower","Like A Rolling Stone","Hey Joe","Blood On The Tracks"],correctAnswer:"All Along The Watchtower"
  },
  {
    question: "Before Rod Stewart went on to have a successful solo career he was a major part of what band?",
    answers:["The Cars","The Doors","The Faces","The Talking Heads"],
    correctAnswer:"The Faces"
  },
  {
    question: "Which is the greatest selling album of all time?",
    answers:["Thriller","Back In Black","Eagles-Their Greatest Hits 1971 - 1975","Dark Side Of The Moon"],
    correctAnswer:"Eagles-Their Greatest Hits 1971 - 1975"
  },
  {
    question: "Who played slide guitar in the Allman Brothers Band?",
    answers:["Duane Allman","Greg Allman","Dicky Betts","Butch Trucks"],
    correctAnswer:"Duane Allman"
  },
  {
    question: "What was Elvis's highest grossing single?",
    answers:["All Shook Up","It's Now Or Never","Suspicious Minds","Jailhouse Rock"],correctAnswer:"It's Now Or Never"
  }
];



